http://www.princetonwatches.com/pages/privacy-policy-1

Skip to content
Sign up for deals and promotions
Join our mailing list for deals and promotions.
Harve Benard
Indigo Thread Co.
Gems en Vogue
Indigo Thread Co.
Scope of this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how Princeton Watches (“Princeton”) uses, shares and protects the personal information we collect through Princeton’s websites (“Websites”), including princetonwatches.com ("princetonwatches.com") and affiliated websites containing links to this Privacy Policy, Princeton’s telephone ordering and interactive voice response services (“Telephone Services”) and Princeton’s mobile and other applications (“Applications”) (hereinafter, the Websites, Telephone Services, and Applications are referred to collectively as the “Princeton Systems”). This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated into the Princeton Terms of Use.
Your Consent to This Privacy Policy
By browsing or using the Princeton Systems, you are agreeing to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Princeton Systems.
This Privacy Policy May Change
We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version on princetonwatches.com. Your use of the Princeton Systems following any such change constitutes your agreement that all personal information collected from or about you through the Princeton Systems after the revised Privacy Policy is posted will be subject to the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.
The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You may access the current version of this Privacy Policy at any time by clicking on the link marked "Privacy" at the bottom of each page on princetonwatches.com and other locations in the Princeton Systems.
Questions Concerning Our Online Privacy Practices
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please email us at sales@princetonwatches.com or write to us at Princeton Watches, c\o Legal Department, 6740 Shady Oak Road, Eden Prairie, Minnesota 55344.
Privacy Notices
This Privacy Policy may be supplemented or amended from time to time by "privacy notices" posted on the Princeton Systems. For example, certain pages of Princeton’s Websites may contain privacy notices providing details about the ways we use or share the personal information we collect on those pages.
What Information Does Princeton Collect?
Information You Give Us
We collect the personal information you knowingly and voluntarily provide when you use the Princeton Systems – for example, the information you provide when you register, create an account, sign-in, search, apply for credit, participate in a contest or questionnaire, submit reviews, sign up for our e-mails, communicate with customer service, or purchase products, services and other retail offerings (“Merchandise”). Depending on how you use the Princeton Systems, you may supply us with information such as your name, address, phone number, email address, credit card information, or information about people to whom purchases will be shipped (for example, a gift recipient).
Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser
We collect information that is sent to us by your web browser, including but not limited to your IP address or device identifier, the address of the web page you were visiting when you accessed the Princeton Websites or Applications, the date and time of your visit, your location, and information about your computer's operating system or mobile device. Please check your browser or mobile device if you want to learn what information your browser or mobile device sends or how to change your settings. We use this information in part to create statistics that help us improve the Princeton Websites and Applications and make them more compatible with the technology used by our visitors. If you have created a user identity on one of your visits to the Princeton Websites or Applications or if you access the Princeton Websites or Applications by clicking on a link in an email we have sent you, we may combine the information provided by your browser with other information that identifies you personally.
Information We Collect Using Cookies and Other Web Technologies
We use "cookies" and other web technologies to collect information and support certain features of the Princeton Websites or Applications. For example, we use these technologies to collect information about the ways visitors use the Princeton Websites or Applications —which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page. Cookies and other web technologies are also used to support the features and functionality of the Princeton Websites or Applications, for example, to track the contents of your shopping cart as you move from page to page. These technologies also permit us to keep a record of your previous choices and preferences so that we can personalize your shopping experience and save you the inconvenience of reentering information already in our database. Generally, the information we collect using these web technologies does not identify you personally; however, it may be linked to information that does identify you personally, such as the information you provide when you make a purchase or register to use a special feature of the Princeton Websites or Applications. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. You may also delete our cookies as soon as you leave the Princeton Websites or Applications. Although you are not required to accept our cookies when you visit the Princeton Websites or Applications, if you set your browser to reject cookies, you will not be able to use all of the features and functionality of the Princeton Websites or Applications.
Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in some web browsers, allowing users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. At the present time, there are not yet established universal standards for recognizable DNT signals and, therefore, the Princeton Websites and Applications do not recognize DNT.
Information We Collect From Other Sources
We may supplement the information collected through the Princeton Systems with information we collect in other ways. We may also supplement the information collected through the Princeton Systems with information from third parties, including data brokers. By supplementing your profile with information from other sources, we are better able to provide Merchandise recommendations and special offers that may be of genuine interest to you. We may also use this additional information to further personalize the Princeton Systems and improve your shopping experience.
Use of Cookies and Similar Technologies by Our Advertising Agents
Princeton may use third-party advertising companies to place online advertisements on our behalf at websites other than princetonwatches.com or Princeton’s other Websites. These advertising companies may use cookies and web beacons (also known as "pixel tags") to target and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements. For example, our advertising companies may place web beacons on their clients' websites. When you visit these websites, the web beacon "tags" your computer with a "cookie" that collects and stores information about your visit to their clients’ websites. Our advertising companies use the information they collect about your use of their clients' websites to customize the advertisements you see when you visit their clients' websites, called interest-based advertising. Our advertising companies' use of cookies and web beacons is covered by their privacy policies, not by this Privacy Policy.
You have choices with respect to online advertising and can tell us and/or our partners not to collect and use this information. Note that if you choose to opt out, you may continue to see ads on princetonwatches.com and other websites, but they will not be based on how you browse and shop. To opt out of receiving interest-based advertising from third-parties, visit the following websites:
http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/ http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/
As noted above, you can also prevent some automatic collection of information by disabling cookies on your web browser. For more information, see “Information We Collect Using Cookies and Other Web Technologies”, above.
Use of Personal Information Collected through the Princeton Systems
We may use the personal information we collect through the Princeton Systems for reasons including:
to fulfill your order for Princeton Merchandise;
to provide you with the information or Merchandise you request or purchase;
for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes;
to register your purchase with the manufacturer or service provider;
to provide you with effective customer service;
to provide you with a personalized shopping experience;
to display personalized advertising when you visit the Princeton Websites or Applications or third-party websites;
to contact you with commercial and promotional messages, including but not limited to special offers and other information we believe will be of interest to you;
to contact you with information and notices related to your use of the Princeton Systems or your purchases;
to invite you to participate in surveys and provide feedback to us;
to better understand your needs and interests;
to improve the content, functionality and usability of the Princeton Systems;
to improve our Merchandise offerings;
to improve our marketing and promotional efforts; and
for any other purposes we identify in a specific privacy notice or other communication to you.
Our Corporate Affiliates
We may share your personal information with our subsidiaries and parent and sister corporations (our "corporate affiliates"), who may use this information to contact you with information and offers they believe will be of interest to you. The corporate affiliates' use of your personal information shall be subject to this Privacy Policy.
Our Service Providers
We may share your personal information with companies that perform services on our behalf. Our service providers are required by contract to protect the confidentiality of the personal information we share with them and to use it only to provide services on our behalf.
Other Business Partners and Selected Vendors.
We work closely with certain business partners (including but not limited to Issuer, defined above) and carefully selected vendors to provide you with access to their Merchandise and other offerings. We may share personally identifiable information about you with these business partners or selected vendors, and they may use this information to offer you Merchandise that they believe will be of interest to you or to address any questions or concerns that you may have about their Merchandise.
Extended Warranty Providers and Other Vendors
If you purchase an extended warranty in connection with Merchandise you purchase through Princeton, we will share with the company that provides the extended warranty the information it needs to service the extended warranty and offer you renewal and other options.
Business Transfers
Information submitted to Princeton or the Princeton Systems will become part of our normal business records. Your personal information may be transferred to another company (either a corporate affiliate or an unrelated third party) that has acquired substantially all the stock or assets of Princeton, one of our corporate affiliates, or one of our operating divisions, for example, as the result of a sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or liquidation.
Government and Legal Disclosures
We may disclose the personal information we collect through the Princeton Systems when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law (or a court order or subpoena); to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce the Terms of Use or other agreements that govern your use of the Princeton Systems; to protect the rights, property or safety of Princeton, our users or others; or to protect your vital interests. If you have purchased Merchandise from us on extended payment terms, it may be necessary for us to file certain information about you with state or local government offices to protect our security interest in that Merchandise or to provide certain information about you to collection agencies in the event of non-payment or a payment dispute.
What Choices Do You Have?
Princeton respects your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use and disclose your personal information. We generally ask you to indicate your choices at the time that you register as a user of princetonwatches.com or another location on the Princeton Systems where you provide your personal information. When you register as a user of the Princeton Systems, you automatically start to receive information, including commercial and promotional messages, periodically via e-mail. You may "opt-out" of receiving our commercial and promotional emails at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in the particular email. You may also manage your subscription and email preferences by clicking on "Sign In" on princetonwatches.com, Princeton’s Applications or by sending us an email. To send us an email, please email us at sales@princetonwatches.com.
For more information on your choices concerning online tracking and online advertising, see the “Use of Cookies and Similar Technologies by Our Advertising Agents” above.
How Can You Update or Correct Your Personal Information?
You may update your account settings information, including your name, contact information, credit card information, shipping and billing addresses, and subscription and email preferences at any time by clicking on "Sign In" or “Account Log In” at princetonwatches.com. You can change your account settings at any time and as often as necessary. When you update your account settings, we may keep a copy of the prior version for our records. You are responsible for ensuring that we have up-to-date and active contact information for you on file, including email address and any telephone number.
Minors who post comments or other information to the Princeton Websites or Applications so that it is visible to others are able to request that the information be removed by contacting us by email at sales@princetonwatches.com or writing to us at Princeton Watches, c\o Legal Department, 6740 Shady Oak Road, Eden Prairie, Minnesota 55344. Note that although we can help make sure the information is no longer visible on the Princeton Websites or Applications, this does not ensure complete or comprehensive deletion of your information from Princeton’s internal systems and/or other websites and services beyond our control.
Special Notice to California Residents
We may share some of your information with third-party companies with whom we have contracts to provide Merchandise and/or with companies that use the information for their marketing purposes. California law permits you to request, once per calendar year, information regarding the disclosure of your personal information (specifically, categories of information and the identity of the third parties) during the previous calendar year to any third party for its own direct marketing purposes. To make this request, please contact us as explained above.
Security
Princeton has implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure with industry standard measures in place to protect the security of the personal information we collect through the Princeton Systems. For example, we use Transport Layer Security (“TLS”) to encrypt your credit card information as it travels over the Internet, and no credit card information is stored in Princeton’s infrastructure. It is important that you understand, however, that no website or database is completely secure or "hacker proof." You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse, for example, by protecting your passwords. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to the Princeton Systems. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Princeton Systems.
Links to Other Web Sites
Princeton’s Websites may contain links to other websites operated by Princeton and its corporate affiliates and service partners. They also may contain links to websites that are owned and operated by unrelated third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to personal information collected through the Princeton Systems. It does not apply to personal information collected on any website that does not contain a link to this Privacy Policy, nor to any website operated by any third party. These websites have their own policies regarding privacy. We recommend you review the privacy policy posted on any website you visit before using the website or providing any personal information about yourself.
Children and Minors
The Princeton Systems are not directed at nor targeted to children under the age of 13. We do not use the Princeton Systems to knowingly solicit personal information from or market to children under age 13 absent verifiable parental consent. If you are under 13 years of age, you should not submit any personal information to us. If you become aware of any personally identifiable information we have collected from children under age 13, please contact us as described above under “Questions Concerning Our Online Privacy Practices.”
Opens in a new window.
